justrage.com 2005-03-10

# justrage.com - Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

We have created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website. 

**Information is Automatically Logged**

This site uses a visitor statistics package that logs the following information upon each page access: userid, user_agent, IP address, host, browser type, computing platform, date and time, page(s) viewed, referer, request type, and query_string. We use this information to help diagnose possible problems with our server, administrate our website, and to gather statistic information about our visitors. The information we collect in this manner will never be given nor sold to a third party unless we are required to do so by a court of law. 

**Cookies**

This site uses cookies to recognize you and automatically log you in each time you visit our site. 

**Registration Forms**

Our website's registration form requires users to give us thier contact information (i.e. an email address). This contact information is used to validate the user's account. This enables the website administrators to provide moderation for the various public and private features of this website, and to get in touch with the user when necessary. This contact information will never be given or sold to a third party unless we are required to do so by a court of law. We use this data to tailor our visitors' experience on our site by showing them content that we think they might be interested in and such according to their preferences. 

**External Links**

This website contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices nor the content of such websites. 

**Public Posts**

This site makes message posting services available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. While we do our best to ensure only appropriate information is posted, we cannot and do not assume responsibility for your postings. All postings are the property of their respective authors. All submissions are subject to our editorial control, and all editorial changes will be indicated as such. 

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. 

**Data Quality/Access**

This site gives users control over the experience and content that they may have provided. Users can freely request for the modification or deletion of any content that they have posted. Users may also have the ability to customize various aspects of the look and feel of the site. 

**Limitation of Liability**

We are **NOT** liable for any damages caused by any of this website's content, regardless of who provides it. 

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this website, or your dealings with this website, you may contact the following person: 

Last Updated Monday, February 07 2005 @ 09:34 AM CST [](http://www.justrage.com/staticpages/index.php/privacy/print)
